Kevin. What's your ideal woman like?
Kevin. 你理想的女人是怎样?
Oh,she's tall.Beautiful...
Oh,她高挑. 美丽...
With long blonde hair... Blue eyes...
长着长长的金发...蓝色的眼睛...
Dresses well...
穿得很好
I can't believe you two.
我不能够相信你们俩.
Is that all you think about?
那是全部你们考虑的?
Yes.
Why,Wendy? What's your ideal man like?
why,Wendy? 什么是你理想的男人?
He's generous and intelligent
他是宽宏大量的 和聪明的
and kind and sensitive and dependable.
和善良的 和善解人意的 和可靠的.
He's medium height and weighs not one ounce over 175 pounds.
他是中等高度 并且体重没有一盎司(ounce)超过175磅.
That's ah...
那是 ah...
79 kilos.I'm your man,Wendy.
79公斤. 我是你的(理想的)男人, Wendy.
That's ah.. twelve and a half stone.
That's ah...十二和半英石(stone)
I'm afraid that's me,Wendy.
我恐怕那是我, Wendy.
You two. And you're both so modest.
你们俩. 并且你们两者都如此地谦虚.